Robin Prajapati

+1 3322013615 | | prajapatirobin123@gmail.com | Norfolk, VA 23508

SUMMARY

Experience in developing responsive applications based on Node.js, Express.js, Vue.js, Vuetify, Bootstrap and state management tools. Developed applications on multi-domain platforms such as Institutions and government sectors. Experience in developing Machine Learning applications using ML algorithms, Neural networks, Tensorflow frameworks and python Libraries such as scikit-learn, numpy and pandas. Experience in development and deployment of decentralised applications based on Ethereum and Hyperledger Fabric. Experience in the development of multi-platform mobile applications based on Flutter and Nativescript using different state management design patterns.

SKILLS

C, C++, Python, Javascript, HTML5, CSS, Solidity, Blockchain, Machine Learning, Node.js, Express.js, Vue.js, JQuery, Flutter Nativescript, Hyperledger, Ethereum, Socket.io, MongoDB, MySQL, Firebase, Unix, Linux (current), Windows, Postman, VScode, Bitbucket, Github.

EXPERIENCE

Graduate Teaching Assistant, Old Dominion University, January 2021-May 2021 Norfolk, VA

Taught Cybersecurity to under-grad student and also helped them in resolving their doubts related to cybersecurity.

Intern, The Sparks Foundation, September 2020-October 2020

Explored Data science by working on supervised learning, Unsupervised Learning, Decision tree Algorithms and Business Analytics.

Research Intern, Old Dominion University, July 2019-August 2019 Norfolk, VA

I had implemented two project one is Repo Generation System (Automated the interaction with github using the web interface) and the other is the research project, in which I had worked on the aggression detection for Alzheimer's patient using the various machine learning algorithm like naive bayesian, k-means clustering and pca.

ACADEMIC PROJECTS

Speaker Accent Recognition, March 2021-May 2021

Developed Binary classification model, where the model is able to correctly classify whether the speaker is US speaker or Non-US speaker based on the given audio input to the model with the accuracy of about 84%.

CHKD (Children's Hospital of the King's Daughter) website, September 2020-November 2020 Developed the website with role based authentication system, the user can view and edit the details of their own according to the role-based permission. Also implemented the chatting stuff in between the patients and the doctors for the prescription details, I also implemented the status of the surgery, where the patients can view their current, past as well as the future status.

Research Intern, Old Dominion University, July 2019-August 2019 Norfolk, VA

I had implemented two project one is Repo Generation System (Automated the interaction with github using the web interface) and the other is the research project, in which I had worked on the aggression detection for Alzheimer's patient using the various machine learning algorithm like naive bayesian, k-means clustering and pca.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Master of Science

Computer Science, Old Dominion University, Norfolk VA Expected in December 2022

Bachelor of Science

Information Science, Acharya Institute of Technology, Bangalore August 2020